LEAD PRODUCT DESIGNER

<u>VDTLV.ME</u> · <u>CONTACT@VDTLV.ME</u> · <u>LINKEDIN.COM/IN/VDTLV</u>

Product designer with more than 4 years of experience. I've worked with both B2B and B2C, mid-market and startup companies from different fields (e-commerce and sports tech). I've led projects across web and mobile and have been involved in all stages of the project lifecycle, from strategy and research to visual design and testing. I design pleasant and understandable user-friendly interfaces that enhance intuitive user experiences, directly influencing business growth. And find the most excitement in working on complex projects with a high level of ambiguity.

EXPERIENCE

LEAD PRODUCT DESIGNER, FITMOST - 09/2022 - PRESENT

- Prioritized the product design backlog in collaboration with the CPO in alignment with the team's quarterly plans.
- I launched features informed by unit economics and tracked the results using Amplitude, Mindbox, and MySQL. This initiative led to a 30% reduction in CAC and a 30% increase in viral users growth.
- · Initiated qualitative researches, and improved existing user flows.
- · Implemented quantitative research into the design process.
- I designed the onboarding process for studios, resulting in a 5x growth across cities in the previous year.
- Introduced a design system and semantic palette, which is used not only by designers but developers as well.

MIDDLE UI/UX DESIGNER, RIGHTONTREK - 09/2021 - 09/2022

- Developed the ecosystem within e-com. Established interactions between parts of the service.
- Managed and developed the design system.
- Reviewed the work of the designers on the team, and defined goals and metrics of success with the product manager.

UI/UX DESIGNER, CHEF BAITY - 07/2020 - 08/2021

- Developed web interface for food delivery service. Built a website with CMS and set up a CRM integration.
- Designed brand book and guidelines for social media, printed materials, documentation and merch.
- · Conducted A/B tests and qualitative research.

OTHER PROJECTS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

WINNER OF VK HACKATHON - 12/2024

 Developed a mini app, an AI consultant for VK market products, in collaboration with developers. I conducted user research and focused on unit economics and user interface design for this mini app.

WINNER OF RUSSPASS HACKATHON - 05/2024

Collaborated with backend and frontend developers to build an AI chatbot, where I
designed user flows to enhance the user experience.

DESIGN MENTOR, GOHELPER.IO - 01/2023 - 04/2024

- Provided case studies and educational tasks for product design course.
- · Shared feedback on students' researches and created designs.

CONTENT STANDARDISATION VOLUNTEER, UTEMPLA - 10/2022

 I contributed to the MVP launch of UTEMPLA by developing automation tools to transform raw text into standardized samples.

EDUCATION

DATA-DRIVEN PRODUCT MANAGEMENT SIMULATOR GO PRACTICE COURSE – 2024

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES IN DESIGN ITMO UNIVERSITY — BA, 2021

SKILLS

Product thinking, Product vision, UX research, Qualitative and Quantitative Research, B2B, B2C, Mindbox, Amplitude, Google Analytics, SQL

Product Design, Mentorship and Training, Communication Design, User Experience (UX), Research, Design System, Accessibility, User Interface (UI), Mobile- & Webdesign, Iconography, Information Architecture, Wireframes, Prototyping, Figma, Sketch, CSS, HTML, Adobe Suite